你的馍很差,夥
You look like shit,man.
我]事
I'm all right.
你就嘴硬吧
Keep telling yourself that.
@?
That right there?
@是本市有史以 最好的家庭作I了
That is the best homework assignment the city ever came up with.
是啊 我和孩子L末就去
Yeah.Me and the kid start this weekend.
除非又被阿曼_r著了
That is,of course,unless Amanda botches everything up,like she always does.
我可以莫妮卡o她打 她PS一直很好
I could have Monica give her a call.They always got along pretty well.
xx你的好意,不^你最好是e管
You know,Eddie,I appreciate it,but it's best if you stay out of it.
R克,什N事?
Yo,D'Mac,what's up?
我有d趣 你有什N情r?
Yeah,I'm interested.What do you got?
海底人 Boyle Heights^
Haitians.Boyle Heights.
我知道那地方
Yeah,I know the place.
3-B,知道了
3-B,got it.
有毒品正在交易
Ya yo changing hands.
你真想招惹@混蛋?
You really wanna mess with this low-level shit?
,我走
Yeah,let's go.
- 情r不e?- 一切都好
- Are we good?- All signs point to it.
你l收?
Which one of you gentlemen is gonna sign for this?
衣服不e
Nice suit.
fl生g堵了?
I heard there was a problem with the toilet?
好了 我有不到一小r 由戆
All right,fellas.We got less than one hour.Let's go.
走_
Move.
- 警察,不S!- 的!
- Police,freeze!- Shit!
- 抓住他!- 趴在地上!
- Get him!- On the floor,God damn it!
e跑!
Stop!
不S!
Don't move!
- 抓住他了?- 他跑了
- You got him?- He got away.
- 什N?- 他跑了!
- What?- He got away!
死的!
Shit!
ef,芸 什N都ef!
Not a word,Welles.Not a goddamn word!
混蛋!
Son of a bitch!
行
Now.
怎N
What the...
L 梯出故障了
Chief.We got a problem with the elevators.
- 趴下!- e起!
- Get down!- And stay down!
注意了,都o我趴在地上!
Now that I have your attention,get on the floor,right now!
- 都趴下 - e激!
- Take it easy,take it easy.- Everyone!
- 你也趴下!
- You,too,come on!- Get down!
都@示 "出F故障"
Everything's reading "Malfunction."
- 怎N回事?- 不知道
- The hell is this?- I don't know.
我不想人!
We're not here to hurt you!
老老的就不有事,了?
You stay calm,you go home for dinner,you understand me?
e看我
Don't look at me.
都不S!趴在地板上!
Nobody move!And get down on the floor!
e叫!
Shut up!
有人不老啊
We got a naughty one here.
天!FedCaly行
Jesus!FedCal,the bank.
不的女孩 F在只能打了
All right,that's it,bad girl.Now we get to go make a phone call.
45分了!
Forty-five!
- 14新l道峋- 就f正在l生劫
- News 14 hotline.- Tell them there's a robbery in progress.
我在洛杉市^的FedCaly行
I'm from the FedCal Bank,downtown LA.
正l生劫案
There's a robbery in progress.
- 劫匪在y行?- 在
- Are they still in the bank?- They're still...
劫匪
Are they...
我快走吧
Come on,man,let's get out of here.
我走!
Let's go!
跳!
Jump!
趴下!
Get down!
各位,l生y行劫案 我去市^
Hey,guys,a bank robbery.We're headed downtown.
@就去!
Let's go,now!
- 我在理!
- I got the back!- I'm on it!
他走翘蓦x_的!
They left the bank using the stairs!
所有出口已封i
All exits are covered.
看,琼上,有警l在那Y降落!
Look,on the roof,a guard!Land it!
- 我]得到S可 - 我是最先到F龅 快降落
- We're not cleared for this.- We're first on the scene.Land us,now.
走吧!
Let's go!
拿出z像C
Get the camera out.
你怎N?
Are you okay?
- 趴在地上!
- No!- Get on the ground!
趴在地上!R上下直升C!
Get on the ground!Get out of the chopper now!
也趴在地上!
Take a seat next to your friends!
真是一群笨蛋!好拥
What a bunch of dummies!Good boy.
只有一能值z影!
Nothing but glorified paparazzi!
我走吧!
Get us out of here!
14l道走e路了
There goes Channel 14 going the wrong way.
所以他是最後到F
That's why they're in last place.
Y弗斯,你自由了
Come on,Rivers,you're a free man.
可以走了
You're out of here.
有空?
Any vacant floors?
26诱在b修
Yeah,26 is under construction.
那一佑z像^?
You got security cameras on that floor?
b修r候不有
Not in the construction area.
法t去z查一下
Have forensics go over it.
你要{取很多人的指y
You'll pick up prints from half the damn city.
但也]k法
Do it anyway.
- ]} - 好
- You got it.- Okay.
跑很快 成T}s
Went down pretty fast.We got a mixed crew.
其中一人有外地口音
Apparently,one of the guys had some type of an accent.
- 走了多少X?- 200多f
- How much did they take?- North of two million.
有的n票可能有
Some of the bills might be marked.
f不定能因此找到
Who knows,maybe we'll get lucky.
劫匪用C4炸破牧穗梯
So,they used C-4 to knock out the elevators.
留物送去化了
Residue's being sent to the lab now.
xx 自硬,rg算精_
Thanks.Automatic weapons,precision timing.
定向爆破 其中y度可想而知
Shape charges.Degree of difficulty is off the charts.
毫o疑,他是高手
They were hot shit,no doubt about that.
抓住高手 感X才更爽
It'll make it that much sweeter when we take them down.
是啊
Yeah.
什N事?
What is it you want?
你是xw?
You Sergei?
OzY的米哈伊洛S奇我淼
Mikhail,from in the joint,sent me.
好
Okay.
你正在玩啊?
Y'all having fun,huh?
e,小子
Not so fast,my man.
出示C件
Show me ID.
美!美!
USA!USA!USA!
老c
Think about it.
en
Cool down.
我有伏特加 有事好商量?
We...We have vodka and take care of business,huh?
估你@Nf
That's what I thought you'd say.
我有了一大PX
We've got some serious stacks now.
真是爽啊
And I mean it's love,baby.
- 行吧 - 得了
- Yeah,we did all right.- All right,my ass.
@是我最大的一P劫,你看起K不怎N高d
Our biggest heist yet,and you,you don't seem too jazzed.
我挺高d
No,I'm good.
挺高d
I'm good.
爸爸昨晚打了
Listen,Dad called last night.
我去探望他
He wants us to come see him.
不行 芸
No.Hell,no,Jake.
我在OzY^爸爸 我去^少管所
I've been to see Dad in jail.I've been to juvie.
我再也不去Oz了 不管是榱四,榱税职,
I'm not going back.Not for you,not for Dad,
- 是榱巳魏稳 Q不 - 好,好
- not for anybody.Ever.- Okay,okay.
他有不到五年刑期
He's got less than five.
他出硪葬,
So,when he gets out,
我o他w房子
maybe we build him a house.
- 行?- 行
- Cool?- Cool.
戈登f看有的n票,就掉
Gordon says you find anything marked,burn it.
得不e
Sounds tight.
你弟弟和那N多X在一K 你能放心?
You just gonna leave your kid bro up there with all that paper?
他要是花光了,你打死他就是
If he runs out with it,shoot him.
我正有此意
I will,too.
得@首曲子?
Remember the song?
好
All right.
我不知道怎Nf 我 很忙 你看看
I don't know what to tell you.We're so...We're so busy.Look at this.
假如把隔壁的空房子一起I^,@家多美啊
And if we get that empty space next door,think about how amazing it's gonna be.
- @是什N?- 打_看看
- What's this?- Open it.
天啊
Oh,my God.
真好看
It's beautiful.
你也一雍每
I think you're beautiful,too.
如果你意,
If you'll have me,
我想和你共度一生
I wanna spend the rest of my life with you.
狂妄的砘
Cocky assholes.
像浜昧
Tapes are ready.
看看
All right,let's see what we got.
大d共有20部梯
There's 20 elevators for the lobby.
^低12部,^高8部
Twelve for the lower floors,eight for the uppers.
以22榻
You can cross over at 22.
一天之中,有多少人上下梯?
So,over the course of the day,how many people on and off?
- 1f左右
- Ten thousand,give or take.- Shit.
只看l在b修酉码梯
Well,let's see who got off on the construction floor.
肯定]人
It couldn't have been more than a handful of people.
@]k法 像是根rg淼,不是根淼
Well,it doesn't work that way.These tapes are time-coded,not floor-coded.
@N多人上下梯
All these people getting on and off
我s不知道停在?
and we have no idea what floor we're watching?
是@拥
Yeah.I mean,that's how it works.
你的O控像可真行啊
Come on.This is some system you got here,Chief.
e人的大腔本都@
Most of the buildings in the city are set up this way.
- @NO,真是白V - @我不勐!
- Whoever set it up is an idiot.- Hey,I don't need this!
我可是好心兔
All right,I'm down here trying to help.
他@不是有意的?
Hey.Look,man,he doesn't mean nothing by it,all right?
- xx你前?- 你去死吧
- Thanks for coming by,okay?- Screw you.
是你的不管用 是缺少女人了?
Meds not working or we just need to get you laid?
- 你怎N了?- 你看
- What's the problem?- Look at this.
@是z像^ 他知道梯Y]人
It's a camera.They knew the elevator was empty.
他Υ遣t如指掌
They knew the building.They knew the whole system.
即使看上100小r
Yeah,must be a hundred hours here.
我也看不出什N名堂
We don't know what the hell we're looking for.
大_曼u不是不好,
Not to piss on Grand Cayman,
不^我X得把X存在安的列斯群u的
but I think I can get you an additional 75 basis points
收益能增加75百分c?
in the Dutch Antilles.I say why not?
不^市霾嘧,
Yeah,but the way the markets keep jumping around,man,
l能知道字苤後利率是多少?
another four,six weeks,who knows what the rates'll be?
你看^最新的蟾媪?
And have you seen the latest Bloomberg report?
- 那Y形莶缓 - "蟾"?得了吧?
- Shit is bleak out there.- "Bloomberg reports"?Are you kidding me?
大W生 e想得太多了
Come on,college guys.Let's not over-think it.
是啊 既然安的列斯群uo的利率更高
Yeah,come on.Dutch Antilles wanna pay us more money.
- 考]什N - 我喜g安的列斯群u,
- That's a no-brainer.- I like the Dutch Antilles,
只要y行e在一夜之g破a了就行
as long as the banks don't pack up and take my money overnight.
是把10％的X捐o慈善C?
Of course.10% to the usual charities?
- 然 - 我同意
- Absolutely.- Cool by me.
我租了一架wC 今晚在凡奈斯C銎痫w
I chartered a jet.It's taking off Van Nuys Airport tonight.
l想和我一起走的,@Y有Ｓ猛ㄐ凶C
Anybody wants to come,I got your private parking passes right here.
@就妥了
It'll be sweet.
F在感X人生真好
Man,life's looking pretty good from right here.
我考]一下
I'll let you know later.
好房子 好野
Nice house.Cool view.
好酒
Great scotch.
劫持了新台的直升C 上面M了"AJ"
You know,jacking that news chopper had "A.J." written all over it.
你怎NM淼?
How'd you get in my house?
太瘟
Please.
你提前出z了?
They let you out early or what?
表F良好 提前一年放
Good behavior.About a year early.
不^你都把我忘了吧?
But I guess you guys kind of lost track,huh?
我f^彼此不M 你硎颤N事?
No contact.That's what we agreed upon.So,what's up?
我想再喝一杯
I think I'm gonna have another scotch.
@是好酒 一起喝吧?
It's good shit,John.You gonna drink with me,right?
然
Sure you are.
我之所以碚夷,
You see,I came to you,John,
因槟愕挠X悟比他高
because you the one with that higher consciousness and shit.
- 接著f - 你我有什N事
- All right,I'm listening.- Well,you asked what's up.
我就是想你了
I miss my homies.That's what's up.
此外有一些f~
That,and some unfinished business.
04年劫案你的那份X 都o你留著
Your money from '04 is safe and accruing interest.
~在戈登那Y
Gordon's got the bank account numbers.
莉莉呢?她在l那Y?
What about Lilli?Who's got her numbers?
她F在和芸
She's with Jake now.
我祝福他 我有件事要
Well,good for them.I got a deal we need to discuss.
- 一PIu - _什N玩笑?
- A job.- You're kidding me,right?
你因橛匈Iu碚椅?
You're coming at me with a job right now?
y道我是黹f聊的?
Think I'd come at you on some bullshit?
@是y得的C,s翰 你t解我@人
Once in a lifetime,John.You know me.
我研究^了
I do my homework.
你想我f什N?
All right,so what do you want me to say here?
什N都不用f
You ain't got to say shit.
只要住我是04年劫案中 唯一在翘萆鲜被捕的人
Just remember I was the one left bleeding on that fire escape in '04.
警察ξ矣帽M了k法
And they tried everything they could to flip me.
我也]交代, 因槲易袷匚的fh
I ain't budge,'cause we had a deal.I kept my end.
留著@道疤 我δ阌卸
I kept this,too.You owe me,bro.
δ都有恩
All of you.
我和戈登年收你入的r候
What were you,boosting Camaros back in Riverside
你也就是小混混吧?
when me and Gordon decided to let you in?
e看不起我
So,don't be so quick to write me off.
那好,我和他 明天再M你
All right,I'll talk to the boys and I'll get back at you tomorrow.
@就好 我喜g你家
You do that.Love the place.
不^警笃魈差
Alarm system sucks,though.
你砹
There she is.
我的兄弟 你好?
Hello.How's my baby G doing?
我挺好
I'm good,I'm fine.
- 你馍不e - 我感X不e
- You look good.- I feel good.
- 是?- 是的
- Yeah?Yeah?- Yeah.
t生f你可能下周就Y束戒毒
They tell me maybe you finish the program next week.
@八周很y熬
It's been a tough eight weeks.
放心 @次我肯定能戒掉
Don't worry.I'm gonna do it this time.
我@N想也@N感X
That's what my mind and my body's telling me.
我支持你 你知道的吧?
I'm with you.I'm with you.You know that,right?
- 我不再需要毒品了
- Yeah?- I'm not gonna need these anymore.
我x_戒毒所的r候,
By the time I leave here,
就氐]有毒a了
I'm gonna be cleaner than the day I was born.
你知道我很感x你吧?
You know I'm grateful,don't you?
行了 你也就嘴上@Nff
Stop it.You don't need to say that to me,all right?
- 我的信砹?- 然
- Did you get my letter?- Yeah,sure did.
我一直在念叨
I've been non-stop tripping over this,I tell you.
- 加勒比海?- 看看海水
- Caribbean,huh?- Look at the water.
清澈湛{ 既嘏又鏊
Clear and blue.Cool and warm at the same time.
我只想回到那Y
I've just got to get back there.
等你x_戒毒所,我H自你去
Soon as you're out of here,I'm gonna take you there myself.
- 我保C - 好
- I promise.- All right.
我勰
I love you.
P掉
Turn that off.
我回到家
I know,so I walk into my house.
看他在我家Y,喝著酒
He's standing there,he's drinking my whiskey.
我正想_的
I was gonna shoot him in the back of his head.
_就α
Should've shot him.
@砘出硪惶,就想忠还P
The guy's been out 24 hours,already wants to do a job.
- 真是了 - 我看是有量
- He's crazy.- Or he's got huge balls.
X的事 老鬼肯定心Y有底
Yeah,Ghost doesn't play when it comes to money.
他一向不含糊
He's too smart for that.
- @混蛋]那N精明 - 一定的
- The bastard's not that smart.- That's for sure.
也就有c小明
He's clever,not smart.
我是隔一年才能忠还P
You guys,we always wait at least a year between jobs.
- f明比不上他 - 戈登你和他交往多年吧?
- There's a reason for that.- Gordon,you guys go way back,right?
他可靠?
Think he's being straight up?
年他完全可以供出我,
Ghost could've ratted us out a long time ago,
但他守口如瓶
but he didn't.Kept his word.
等他的那份X拿到手 那就yf了?
What's to stop him from doing exactly that once we give him his cut from '04?
- }就在@Y
- See,that's the problem.- Yeah.
- @是大} - 肯定有什N不
- That's a big problem there.- Something ain't right.
- 我信不^他 - 放心
- I don't trust him.- Relax.
- 他砺 - 我X得他P算好了
- He's trouble.- I think he's onto something,though.
- 他f@是一P大Iu - 我不管他怎Nf?
- He says it's big.- Do I look like I care what he says?
你Q定吧,我都成
Well,whatever you decide to do,I'm down with you.
- 我去w
- All right.- I'm going to the loft.
私人派!
Private party!
- 你去哪?- 你管不著!
- Where you going?- None of your damn business!
- 你好 - 莉莉
- Gentlemen.- It's Lilli.
- l要的酒?- @是送os翰的
- Baby,who ordered the Dom?- That's for Johnny-boy.
酒吧那穿G衣服的女孩送的
It's the girl in the green at the bar.
她很漂亮
She's cute.
- e她掏X - 不行,她要付出代r
- Don't let her pay for it.- No,no,she's gonna pay,man.
@就α 你看我的
This is how it's done.Let me show you.
急什N,大W生 @又不是大W宿舍
Slow down,lvy League.This ain't the frat house,man.
你可真能取笑
Well,that's some funny shit,man.That's some funny shit.
我去去就回
I'll come back up later.
- 老鬼 - 久`了
- Ghost.- It's been a long time,girl.
- 你什Nr候出淼?- 怎N想我了?
- When did you get out?- Why?You miss me?
老鬼 emp她
Ghost.You need to back up.
你激邮颤N 芸
Easy,Jake.Easy.
我真心希望你幸福 我和她的事都是以前了
I wish you guys the best.Really.It's the past.
我碚的是未
I'm here to discuss the future.
e介意
If I may.
我f^明天M你,老鬼
Told you tomorrow,Ghost.
我不是吣d的 只榱苏事
I'm not here to bust any balls.Just business.
]e的
All right
AJ 又y身了?
A.J.Any new tats?
- y了 - 我也是
- Yeah,man,couple.- Me,too.
- 戈登 - 老鬼
- G.- Ghost.
一向可好?
How's my man?
我很好,哥
I'm doing good,mate.
夥沼悬co啊?
Lot of tension in the room,huh?
你有何事?
What do you want,Ghost?
真是的
Goddamn.
F在就f?
It's like that?
F在就f
It's like that.
那我握ff
Well,I'll be brief.
握f就像「偷天Q日」中的大Iu
Let's say we go Italian Job on that ass.
我上钦吧?
Why don't we take this upstairs,Ghost?
好的
Fair enough.
和以前的一 2500―3000f美元
Same plan as before,gentlemen.25 to 30 mil.
@就是能到手的X 不^要抓o
All the cash we can carry.Got to move fast,though.
"抓o," 是什Nrg?
When you say "fast," how fast?
下L二
Next Tuesday.
什N?
What?
老鬼,你我5天之热一v\n?
Ghost,you want us to take down an armored truck in five days?
要先搞到路D才行,
I mean,it's not even worth talking about unless you got the route,
r且路常
and they change the route all the time.
- 我上次就是因此失手的 - 你有路D?
- That's what screwed us last time.- Yeah,man,you got the route?
有 正是下L二的路D
I got it.Exact one from next Tuesday.
有什N}?
Any more questions?
- 你怎N得到的?- 在OzY
- How'd you get it?- In the joint.
我和一俄人交好
I got in good with this Russian.
保o他不受e的囚犯欺
Had the pleasure of keeping them guys from Compton off his ass.
作榛,他Oz外的同夥
In exchange,he had his comrades on the outside
收I了{度T
put the arm down on the dispatcher.
{度T做燃,
So the dispatcher do anything to screw the job up,
他在蹩颂m的家人都被害了
they're wiping out his whole family back at the Ukraine.
也包括牧羊犬
Down to the sheepdog.
我{什N信任@俄人?
Why should we trust the Russians?
他喜g自己的牧羊犬
They love their sheepdogs.
不f笑了,
All bullshit aside,
事成之後除去俄人的份~ 有2500f美元
I'm in for a quarter mil with the Russians out my cut when the job's done.
@你不用管,
It's not your concern,
不必相信俄人 相信自己的婪
so don't trust the Russians.Trust greed.
- 我{什N相信你?- 真是的,AJ
- Why should we trust you?- Well,shit,A.J.
我放出 肯定不急著回去
I'm fresh out.I ain't in no hurry to go back.
再f了,我致镆害自己人呢?
Besides,why would I screw over my guys?
r且我的X在你手Y呢?
Especially when you're holding all my money,right?
那你有什N?
Okay.What about the setup?
光有路D不行,有很多涔ぷ
I mean,there's knowing the route,and then there's the logistics,you know.
芸说心不o道理 5天_太短了
Five days.Jake's right.That's a real,real short fuse.
@就要靠你了
That's where you come in.
你和芸撕嫌一下 肯定有k法的
But I trust that when you and Jake put your heads together,you'll figure it out.
不管植,今晚就o我回
Either way,I need to know tonight.
不值脑,]}
You ain't got the heart to pull it off,a'ight.
把上次的Xo我,我就走人
We'll settle up on the money you owe me,I'm sayonara.
子媚的rg了 xx你的雪茄
Appreciate your time,gentlemen.Thanks for the cigar.
- 戈登,我看看路D - 好
- Hey,G,let me check out that route.- Yeah.
@不是我的L格 太}促了
This is not the way we do things,gentlemen.It's too fast,it's too rushed.
Xm然多,但是感X很勉
It's a lot of money,but this whole thing feels forced.
才5天?5天?
Five days?Five?
是的,只要好了就行
Yeah,man,but,you know,we can get the setup right.
LU大,@利就大
Bet big,win big.
@就是真理
It's the only way to play.
我就是靠劫樯的人
We're takers,gents.That's what we do for a living.
我吃@碗
We take.
@可是一大PX,芸
It's a lot of money,Jake.
- 我正是榱隋X - 你Υ擞邪盐?
- And that's what we're here for.- You sure about this?
如果{查可行的
If it checks out.
如果可行,我干
If it checks out,I'm in.
- 什N事?- 有件事你可能有d趣,
- Yeah,what's up?- Thought you'd wanna know,
你抓住的海地人
your Haitian buddy?
他的律起V你E用暴力
His lawyerjust filed on you for excessive force.
他是大h,不老
All right.The guy was 6'5",he was resisting.
不用暴力怎Nk?
What was I supposed to do?
那看害他的感情了
Yeah,well,you must've hurt his feelings.
y行劫案的事  用碚梯的C4炸{查的怎N恿?
The bank.Hey,listen,what about the C-4 they used to blow the elevators?
^化,是碜热A_州的一家竦V公司,
Well,from the taggants,forensics traced it to a mining company out of Nevada,
大s稍虑氨槐I的
stolen about...About two months ago.
有的n票呢?
All right.And what about the marked bills?
y行o出了清 克斯R上就髡嬉环
Bank finally sent over a list.Max is gonna fax out a memo right now.
我f,
Listen,man,
已好字芰四愫桶⒙_有M?
it's been a couple of weeks now.You hear anDhing from Amanda?
xx你的P心,但我不需要椭
Listen,I appreciate it,but I don't need any help.
我自己能解Q 不^也xx你
We can work it out on our own.But thanks.
那好 我炝
All right.I'll talk to you later.
睦瞎淼穆肪D上看
All right,so,for this route Ghost is talking about.
我唯一的C在@Y
The only place we stand a chance is right there.
- @是什N地方?- 原本是地F中D站
- What's there?- It's an old subway car turnaround.
很大,和街道平行
It's large enough,and it runs parallel to the street.
合m得很 可以在希望大街,
It's kind of perfect.I mean,we can get access on Hope Street,
不^我X得橄齑蠼趾偷谒拇蟮缆房诟好
but I say we hold them up at Olive and Fourth.
嗯
All right.
我要先去那Y{查一下,
And we need to get down there first and get some intel on,
街道情r,流量大小等等,不^看}不大
you know,street patterns,traffic density,that sort of thing,but it looks good.
_定好了爆炸和路面厚度,
Once we determine the blast radius and street density,
我就能算出需要多少C4炸
I can tell you how much C-4 you're gonna need to score.
怎N身?
What about the exits?
正在研究
Work in progress,G.
我先去{查一下,再f
You know,we got to get down there first,check it out.
- 想出滋酌身方案 - ]}
- Give me some exits.- You got it.
- 值煤芎 - 好
- It's good work.- Cool.
- 好了 - 好了
- All right,gang.- Good to go.
和以往一 不y得手
Easy money,baby.Same as before.
X都在前面的\n
All the cash is in the front truck.
後面那v是空的 只是o航
Second truck's totally empty.Just an escort.
奢v各有扇
Two men up front,two men in the back.
邮12口绞 和40口礁衤蹇耸
Pump action 12-gauge and.40 caliber Glocks.
或S是9毫米口
Maybe 9mm.
他的通O淇赡芨倪M了,
They may have upgraded their communication by now,
但是防玻璃]
but the same standard bulletproof windows.
他自以槿fo一失
They ain't gonna know what hit them.
好了 先做上擞
Here we go.Must've taken up the tracks.
就@
That's it.
他做@NIu
Yeah,he's still working it.
也I了v新
Got brand-new wheels to show for it,too.
我走
All right,let's go.
等我的命令
All right,wait for my go-ahead.
- 早上好,弗朗克 不e啊!- 你质颤N?
- Good morning,Franco.Nice wheels!- What do you guys want?
- 趴在上
- Get up against the car.- Turn around.
喂,喂,我是清白的
Hey,hey,hey,hey,I'm clean,man.
e碰我 把你的_走?
Hands off.All right?Why don't you move your car?
你知道热A_州被I的C4炸?
What do you know about some C-4 boosted out of Nevada?
我一c不知道
Nevada?I don't know nothing about that.
出了事,你不可能一c消息不知道
Come on,if it's guns or explosives,you heard something about it.
你若是再被捕,就要判十年
You know,you get busted again,you're facing 10 years minimum.
- 你知道吧?- 我知道@是公共龊
- You know that,right?- I know this is a public place.
我]氖 你是把_走吧?
I ain't done nothing.So,why don't you move your car?
- e胡[了 - 哈奇
- Do me a favor.- Hey,Hatch.
- 你看看!- 什N情r?
- Look at this!- What you got?
- 怎N了?- 弗朗克
- What's that?- Come on,Franco.
- 你的胎扎到子了
- It's a damn shame.- Looks like you caught a nail.
- 胎T了 - 是上
- Yeah,you got a flat.- Twice.
- 拜 - 後湎溲Y有溆幂胎吧?
- Come on.- You got a spare in the trunk,right?
- ,我湍Q胎 - 要z查我的後湎,
- Come on,I'll help you.Come on.- You wanna check my trunk,
先要有搜查C
why don't you go get yourselves a warrant?
{度,第九大道和110街道路口有一v出了故障
Hey,Dispatch,we got a disabled vehicle on 9th and the 110.
多Lrg能到@Y?
How long would it take to get here?
我就在附近
Yeah,right around the corner.
哦,就在附近
You got one in the area.
真是巧啊 一
That's great.It's my lucky day.I'll see you in a minute.
你以槲沂巧底?
You guys must think I'm stupid or something,right?
- _M!- 搞什N啊?
- Bring it in!- Man,what the hell is this?
你至少要用正手段!
Come on!This has got to be illegal!
- eo我下套!
- No.- Entrapment or some shit!
我看@]法_了
This looks like a disabled vehicle to me.
你放心吧
Hey,don't worry about it.
我列清,包括你在後湎涞乃有|西
We'll do a full inventory,including everything in the trunk.
我可不想你f警察偷了你的|西
Yeah,we wouldn't want you accusing the LAPD of stealing anything.
- 拜!- 提供c索,弗朗克
- Hey,come on,all right?Hey!- Give us something,Franco.
- 提供c索吧 - @真是胡[!真是的!
- Give us something.- This here is bullshit!Come on,man!
弗朗克,你怎Nk?
Come on,Franco,what do you wanna do?
你人直就是
You know,you two guys,you're a couple of...
- 把吊起!- 你在质颤N?
- All right,hook it up!- What are you doing?
- pc,@可是新!- 你在质颤N?
- Come on!Be nice,it's a new car!- What are you doing?
好,好,我提供c情r
Okay,okay,okay,all right!I got something for you guys,all right?
- 什N情r?
- Come here.- What do you got?
有@N一些人,想更M一步
There's...They got these guys,they're trying to go upscale.
- 干一P大的 - 什N?
- They're planning something big.- What?
肯定打算干P大的
They're definitely planning something real big.
- 质颤N?- @我不知道
- Like what?- I don't know like what.
但我知道他用到C4炸
But I know they're gonna use a C-4 on the job.
你好?
What's up?
你好
Sup.
你一人淼?
You alone?
就像Yf的那
Like I said on the phone.
]砘
He's clean.
- ]有同夥 - 你就是保_?
- No one.- You Paulie?
就像牌子上的那
Like the sign says.
你想IC4炸?
So,you're the one who wants some C-4?
就像Yf的那
Like I said on the phone.
有人I了一大批 外面都缺
I know,the street's gone dry.Someone bought up a big pile of it.
所以你就碚椅伊?
That what brings you to me?
- 明人
- Smart man.- Yeah.
我看看你的一S可C
So,let me see your category one permit.
S可C?我本以楹芎蔚
Permit?Thought this was supposed to be simple.
]e 只要你有S可C
It is.You got a permit.
我的一C件
My category one.
是的,很
Yeah,it is simple.
我收下X,你什N都得不到
See,we take your money,and you don't get shit.
^!
Get over here!
好了!好了
Hey,whoa!Hey.Come on.
你要是敢 就在你的^上添洞
Move,I put three holes in your head like a bowling ball,big boy.
蔚亩嗪?
Should've kept it simple,huh?
- 我估你需要兔 - 兔?
- Thought you might need some backup.- Backup?
你好像被揍得不p
Looked like you getting your ass kicked.
我你在Y等著
Man,I told you guys to wait in the car.
- 你一人能[平啊?- 我_[平了
- You had it under control,huh?- Yeah,I did,actually.
- C4炸呢?- 在旆垦Y
- Where's the C-4?- It's in the shed.
- 老f在哪?- 在旆垦Y!
- Speak English!Where's the C-4?- It's in the shed!
- 在後面旆垦Y!- 在旆垦Y?
- Back in the shed!- In the shed?
- 在旆垦Y?- 後面旆垦Y
- It's in the shed?- Back in the shed.
在旆垦Y
It's in the shed.
值煤 弗朗克交代了
Nice job squeezing Franco.
不f,他就要坐十年牢了
Looking at 10 years,funny how he gave up that address.
你X得他就是FedCaly行的劫犯?
Think it's the FedCal guys?
使用C4炸的人]警L
Only so many people know how to use C-4,Chief.
- 肯!- 卡沃警官?
- Duncan!- Lieutenant Carver?
- 快走吧,芸!- 我要和芸司官!
- Moving and grooving,Jack!- I wanna speak to Detective Welles!
我F在]rg
I can't do this right now.
我有搜查令
We're executing a search warrant.
志察 公
Police work.Remember what that is?
要詹康戎
Internal Affairs will have to wait.
你H我打,威士 你要M我!
Hey,you call me,Welles.Get back to me!
e逼我去找你!
You don't want me to have to come find you!
你怎N突然磉@Y?
The hell is wrong with you,coming down here now?
我你看一段像
I wanna show you something.
警察趴在地上!
Police,on the ground now!
上!
Go!
威士,我@Y]人
Welles,I got nothing.
哈奇,他去了春天大街!
Hatch,he's coming up on Spring!
天!
Shit!
威士!
Welles!
- 你]事吧?- ]事
- You all right?- Yeah.
死者,伊森温斯基和康斯坦丁温斯基
Our two dead guys,Ethan and Constantine Symanski.
兄弟z 俄黑手h嫌疑人,但是和FedCaly行劫案oP
Brothers.Suspected Russian mob,but they're no good for the FedCal job.
- 槭颤N?- 移民局f劫案l生的r候
- Why's that?- INS said they were being sworn in
他正宣誓成槊公民
as U.S.Citizens at the time of the robbery.
- 原硎叛者?- 是啊
- Couple patriots,huh?- Yeah.
我到碇前他了很多|西
They burned a bunch of stuff before we got here.
只剩下@
This is all that was left.
像是洛杉地D
Looks like a map of LA.
可能
Yeah.Maybe.
看看@些|西 C4炸自硬雷管
Look at this stuff.C-4,automatic weapons,blasting caps.
肯定是渥龃蟀
They were definitely onto something big.
斯台普斯中心,珀欣V,合站
Staples Center,Pershing Square,Union Station.
他想质颤N?
The hell were they up to?
- 可以了 - 芸诉B好了 浜昧?
- We're good to go.- Jake's all connected.You ready?
我浜昧,芪
All right,Jesse,we're up.
演示一下
Show it to us.
好
Nice.
芸e再演示了
All right,tell Jake to stop showing off.
好了,P]吧
All right,man,turn it off.
- 好拥 - 好拥
- Good job.- Good job.
但PI是有3天了,到底能不能行?
But the point is,I mean,can we do it in three days?
不但能行,能很安全
Not only can we do it,but we're gonna play it safe.
我每小r一英,
All right,we're gonna drill at about an inch an hour,
16洞要64小r
16 holes in 64 hours.
分_砀,按照M度
Split the work,keep the schedule.
@rg就只有一天了?
So,that leaves us one last day for prep?
]e 足蛭液芸税惭b路了
Exactly.Enough time for Jake and I to wire.It's good.
好,我o拉威打 看看今晚能不能到那Y
All right,I'm gonna call Rahway and see if we can get down there tonight.
l啊?
Who's there?
戈登!
G!
W米 你怎N砹?你不是在
Naomi.What are you doing here?You're supposed to be at the...
是啊,是啊
I know,I know,I...
- 我先走了 - 好
- Catch up with you later,man.- All right,man.
@Y真好
Wow,look at this place.
@是怎N回事?W米?
What is this?Naomi?
我氐捉涠玖 感X很好
Look,I am really clean now.I feel great.
W米,你f什N呢?
Naomi,what are you talking about?
再多呆一周也]什N用
Look,another week in that place wouldn't have made any difference.
- 我不是f好了?- 行了
- We spoke about this,didn't we?- Come on.
我做的很好
I was doing really well.
他能不能提前走,他同意了
I asked if I could leave early,and they said yes.
不信你打
If you don't believe me,call them.
他fx_戒毒,所以後要有生活目
Look,they told us that when you get out,you got to have a plan.
]有生活目耸遣恍械
Yeah?Without a plan,you're dead.
於是我想到了你,我的目,我回老家
So I started thinking about you and me,our plan,and going home.
F的
And that's gonna happen.
但你需要一周,只要一周
You had one more week,that's all,one more week.
我@滋旌苊
It's a busy time for me,Naomi.
- 你不得了吧?- 我不得了
- You don't remember it,do you?- No,I don't.
看你r多N可 真美
Look at how cute you were.Mum was so beautiful.
r我很幸福
I was truly happy back then.
只有回老家我才算真正康土,才能真正重新_始
I'm not gonna be right until I get back there,so I can start again.
能做到的 只需要3天
And we can.In just three days.
我在工作 我要送你去旅^
I'm working.I need to put you in a hotel.
我住@Y不行?
What?Why can't I stay here?
行 只是F在不合m
You can.It's just a bad time for me.
好?
All right?
好吧
Yeah.
我能看出不是街道地D
Well,I can tell you it's not a street map.
是某N市政工程D
It's some kind of a public works project.
]有⒖底值脑 我也o法_定
But without a reference number,there's no way I can work it out.
好 xx
All right.Thanks.
不客
You got it.
Y弗斯,德朗特
Rivers,Delonte.
靠上去
Put your body in it.
接住,小艾迪 上@
Right here,Eddie.Up with it.
漂亮!@硬
Yes!That's what I'm talking about.
小艾迪 著你叔叔,芸
Hey,Eddie.Take it easy on Uncle Jack,all right?
和 我昨晚{查了一下 想和你
Time out.I did some work last night.Wanted to talk to you.
你要I吐的吐到草地上
Hey,if you're gonna puke,do it on the grass.
爸爸,我打完吧
Come on,Dad,let us finish.
你硖Q我吧?
Yeah,why don't you take my place?
不用了 你接著打球吧,小艾迪
I'm good.Go ahead,keep playing,Eddie.
- 小艾迪的情r好多了 - 好得很
- Eddie looks like he's doing a lot better.- Yeah,he's doing great,man.
他上次透析有一月了
I mean,it's been about a month since his last dialysis.
滋冗不行,然後uu康
Down for a couple days,then he bounces back.I mean...
- 你lF了什N情r?
- So,anyway,what's up?- All right.
你得啄昵绊n居民^的 珠劫案?
You remember the jewelry job in Koreatown,few years back?
劫匪利用囊 逃到另一?
They used wires and went from one building to the other?
一警l抓住了其中一劫匪
Guard got loose.He ended up shooting one of them?
得那警l後沓闪舜笥⑿
Yeah.The guard ended up being like a big hero.
那在翘葜的劫匪?
The perp got shot on a fire escape,right?
叫德朗特Y弗斯,b老鬼
Name's Delonte Rivers,a.k.a.Ghost.
在ChinoOz服刑5年
He just finished serving five at Chino.
他在Oz中的C件 不知怎N到了俄人手Y
And somehow,his prison ID ended up at the Russians.
我在照片上看到的
I saw it in the Polaroids.
你是f@人⑴c了y行劫案?
So,you think this guy's good for the FedCal heist?
不知道 他在y行劫案的天被放
I don't know.He was released the same day the bank was hit.
肯定不只是巧合
There's got to be some type of connection there,right?
克斯 什N事?
Yeah,Max.What's up?
- 早上好,芸 - 你好,莫妮卡
- Morning,Jack.- Hey,Monica.
慢cf
Whoa,whoa,slow down.
- IN代表 - _什N玩笑
- Marketing rep.- You got to be kidding me.
克斯,你卡沃L一o我打
Look,Max,you can just tell Carver he can call me Monday.
我L末不上班
I don't work weekends,okay?
詹空椅
Internal Affairs.
我槟阕鲈顼吧?
Well,can I make you some breakfast,Jack?
不了 我要去接桑迪 我要去⒂^滋名
No,that's all right.I got to pick Sunday up.We're gonna go look at some landmarks.
- L一再 - 再,芸
- I'll see you Monday.- See you,Jack.
今天的作I是去哪Y?
So,what do we got?What's the assignment for today?
先去星光大道,然後一篇⒂^感受
After we go to the Walk of Fame,I'm supposed to write about us going there.
孩子,星光大道算不上名,名不符
Honey,the Walk of Fame's not a landmark,it's a tourist trap.
我知道更好的名 我去拉布Yr青坑,
I got a better landmark.Let's go over to La Brea Tar Pits,
然後再去博物^,
and then afterwards we can go to the museum,
去看看化石
we can look at the fossils.
然後再去「rQ市觥钩h堡
And then after that,we can go to the Farmer's Market and get some burgers.
好主意 我去「rQ市觥钩h堡 喝奶昔
Good idea.Burgers and shakes at the Farmer's Market.
你有什N情r?
Yeah,what do you got for me?
孩子,我要先停下
Sweetheart,we're gonna have to make a stop somewhere first.
我昨晚接到你的以後,{查了Y弗斯的n案,
When I got your message from last night,I pulled Rivers' file,
他今天下午有假面
saw he was due this afternoon.
他@拥淖锓 提前放要安排状面
Cons like him,they're good for a visit or two.
不^四年的一O禁,我看面也]用
But four years of lockdown,I wouldn't bet on him.
就是他 要不要我r住他?
There's your boy now.Want me to hold him?Rattle his cage?
不,是按常戆
No.No,keep it routine.
- 你知道他的住址?- 住在L┑哪破地方
- You got an address on this guy?- Some dump in Long Beach.
住一周左右
Probably good for a week,if that.
好,xx
All right,thanks.
去小|京
Little Tokyo.Let's go.
F在能去博物^了?
Now are we going to the museum?
一就去
Just a sec,honey.We will.
- 要e的?- @要砂
- Anything else?- Give me a couple of these,too.
右
Here,on the right.
- xx - 不客
- Thanks,man.- You got it.
- 你好?- 你硗砹
- What's up?- You're late.
- 面M行的怎N?- 挺好
- How'd the parole meeting go?- We good.
屁大的事要弄的@N麻
You know they try and turn pissing in a cup into a seven-game series.
不^]事了
We straight,though.
- 你要I什N?- пu峁
- Can I help you?- Relish.
- 芪 - 你好?
- Jesse.- What's up?
怎N了?其他人呢?
What's happening?Where the guys?
我出碣I吃的 他都等著我
I'm take-out.They're waiting on me.
好的
Sounds good.
- 拿到了?- 我k事你不放心
- So,did you get it?- Come on,man.It's me.
爸爸你看什N呢?
What are you looking at,Daddy?
一就好
Just a second,honey.
和救援用的一
Same thing the rescue workers use.
操作很
Easy as shit.Works just like a can opener.
- 和{度T^了?- ^了
- Speak to the dispatcher?- Yeah.
^了,今天早上和他M的 放心吧
Yeah,yeah,yeah,I spoke to him this morning.We good.
- f - 路是_定的
- Come on,man.- Hey,the route's a lock,G.
再
Talk to you later.
你是心e人吧,戈登
Hey,man,find you something else to worry about,G.
e心我
I got you,homes.
什N?
What?
坐了,孩子
Hold on to your seat,honey.
不_啊?
What are you doing,idiot?
你找找有P?]有?
You see a pen,baby?No?
看那v{色I了?隔著奢v?
There,you see that blue sedan back there?Two cars back?
- 看了 - 他在跟我
- Yeah.- He's sharking us.
右拐
Make a right.
你有P?
You have a pen,baby?Anything?
再右拐
All right,make another right.
- 他跟定我了 -
- He's staying with us.- Yeah.
我停
Let's pull over.
- 他是什N人?- 不算什N人
- Who are they?- They're just some guys.
- 是警察?- 不可能е孩子
- Is it a cop?- With a kid?
你急著叫我碛惺颤N要o事?
What's so important that you'd drag my ass all the way down here?
- 我找到他了 - l?
- I found him,Hatch.- Who?
y行劫案的劫匪戈登科 看看@砘
Him,FedCal.Gordon Cozier.I mean,look at that.
身高,w型,臃合
Same height,same build,same everything.
先等等 你f什N?
Wait,hold on.What are you talking about?
- 你怎N得出@一Y?- Y弗斯去⒓蛹籴面,
- Where's all this coming from?- I followed that guy,Rivers,
然後我跟了他
from his parole meeting.
- 他在商I^下了出租 - е孩子跟?
- And he gets out of a cab downtown.- With Sunday?
你在x「年度最佳父H」?
What,are you gunning for Father of the Year now?
我在上,看他去了一峁
And from my car,I see him go to this hot-dog stand.
科梢苍 Y弗斯背χ我
And Cozier's there.Now,he's got his back to me.
但我肯定他o了科墒颤N|西
But I swear I see Rivers pass something to him.
^了一一T摩托的
A second later,this guy on a motorcycle,he looks at Cozier.
在x_以前看了科梢谎,
And then right before he takes off,bam,
和y行劫匪是同一手
the same gesture the asshole used in the bank.
然後我跟科 抄下了他的牌
And then I followed Cozier and got his license plate number.
看你的 用P的?
Yeah,it's very official.What is that,crayon?
我肯定就是他
Look,man,I'm telling you,it's him.
可你看不他的 就]有C
Except you can't see his face.The guy's got a clean sheet.
他只是有前科的人
Come on,man,you follow an ex-con
也]⒓鱼y行劫,你跟他到峁?
who's no good for the bank job to,what,a hot-dog stand?
- 然後他和某人面
- Then he meets somebody...- Listen to me.
也S了面,也S]面
Maybe he meets somebody there,maybe he doesn't.
- 也S他fo他什N|西 - 著,我告V你我r在那
- Maybe he passes something...- Look,Hatch,I'm telling you I was there.
I了一пu峁,
...and buys a hot-dog with ketchup and relish,
- 然後一T托的
- and then,some guy on a motorcycle says...- Call me crazy.
"告e," 然後走人了
"So long," and rides off.
就{@些你能C明什N呢?
Come on,man,give a brother a break.Are you kidding me?
我能去「rQ市觥?
Can we still go to the Farmer's Market,Daddy?
孩子,Σ黄 天
Baby,I'm sorry.Geez.
]想到@N晚了 我可以去e的地方吃
I can't believe it's this late.We can go eat somewhere else.
只要再^一 你想去哪憾伎梢
Just gonna take a few minutes here.Wherever you want.
真是的
Shit.
你知道你爸爸很勰惆?
Your daddy loves you very much,you know that,right?
- e忘了@一c?- 好的
- Don't ever forget that,okay?- Okay.
你要有可靠的C,芸
Take care of the real stuff,Jack.
我吃比_,如何?
Hey,how about some pizza,huh?
我只想回家
I just wanna go home.
走吧
Let's go.
什Nr候的事?
Well,when'd it happen?
]事 ]事 如果她想回砟忙,
No,no,no.It's all right.If she comes back,do me a favor,
M量把她留住,吉姆,再o我打
you just keep her there,all right,Jimmy,and you call me.
不能她x_旅^ 知道?
She doesn't leave the hotel.Do you understand me?
好
All right.
W米?
Naomi?
我在旅^o吉米留了些X 他]放M保U
I left Jimmy some money at the hotel.He didn't put it in the safe.
- 她把X拿走了?- 她拿著X走了 真是的!
- She took it?- She's gone and so is the money.Shit!
- 你质颤N?- 我要停
- What you doing,mate?- I'm pulling over.
- 槭颤N?- 因槟阆肴フ宜
- Why?- 'Cause you got to find her.
今晚隧道的活我替你
I'll take your time in the tunnel tonight.
- xx了 - 客馐颤N
- Thanks.- You got it.
真是的
Damn it.
- 上面舒服?- 得了吧
- How's it hanging?- Funny guy.
好,下戆
All right,come on down.
我明早大忠
We'll go hot tomorrow morning.
@天拥氐
This is gonna be lovely.
嗨,戈登
Hey,G.
浜昧?
We good?
一切都好
All signs point to it.
- 有W米的消息?- ]有
- Any word from Naomi?- No.
我X得她@次真的走了
This time,I think she's gone.
她不有事的
She'll turn up fine.
你楹芜@N肯定?
What makes you so sure?
你是她唯一的H人,不下你的
If I had any family left,that's where I'd be.
如果明天有什N差e 我不能他跑了
You know,if anything goes wrong tomorrow,we can't let him walk away.
他能把04年的事供出去
He could still hang us for '04.
我可以邮
I'll bring the insurance.
你砹 你好,老鬼?
There he is.How's it going,Ghost?
好得很
I can't call it,gentlemen.
- 你好?
- Yeah.- What's happening?
- 戈登 - 好啊
- G.Cool.- Yeah,man.
又能忠还P了 感X真好就像回到了那鞍
Feels good to be back in action again.It's like old times,huh?
事成之後我在哪面?
So,where we meeting at after the drop?
斯考特正在_定 我明天告V你
Scott's giving me the information.I'll let you know tomorrow.
「LL绲淖涛丁
"Come sip from the cup of destruction."
- 成吉思汗的 -  我崇拜的人之一
- Genghis Khan.- Yeah.One of my heroes.
想得到什N,他就去Z取
Saw what he wanted,reached out and took it.
我明天要做的事也一
Like us,tomorrow.
我也一
Just like us.
- 榱嗣魈 - 榱嗣魈
- To tomorrow.- To tomorrow.
榱嗣魈
To tomorrow.
喂?
Yeah?
慢cf 什N?你在哪?
Slow down,slow down.What?Where are you?
好的 我@就去
All right.Wait,no,no,I'm coming.I'm coming.
k公室在哪?
Where do I find Processing?
M去那T 沿著S就到
Through the far door.Follow the yellow line.
副警Lk公室在哪?
Where's Vice?
下侨サ叵率
Take the stairs to the basement.
我上周收到y行n票清蔚髡,
We got your fax last week about the bank bills,
查到@混蛋手上有不少百元大n,
so when we nailed this scum with a bunch of fresh hundreds,
就o你打了
thought we'd call you.
@混蛋?不吧
This low-life?You gotta be kidding me.
他和女友u毒品的r候被我抓住了
He was hustling some stolen shit with his girlfriend when we stopped him.
n票都]做,但我估是的X
None of the bills were marked,but we figure they gotta be from some job.
你他了?
Did you question him?
]有 他情w不
No.He didn't go easy.
也抽了很多毒品 我想等他先平o一下
He's high as hell,too.We decided to let him chill.
好 我和他
All right.Let me talk to this guy.
我]功夫看你演 你的n票哪淼?
All right,I don't have time for this bullshit.Where did you get the bills?
不用兔!
I got him!
再你一遍 你的n票哪淼?
I'm not gonna ask you again.Where did you get the bills?
- 是J款的X!- 胡f!
- It was a loan,man,it was a loan!- A loan.Bullshit!
f是l lo的
I want a name.Give me a name.
- W米 - W米什N?
- Naomi.- Naomi what?
- W米什N啊?她姓什N?- 不知道!我JR她
- Naomi what?She got a last name?- I don't know,man!I just met her.
也{查^她了?
You bust her,too?
,她叫W米科
Yeah,her name's Naomi Cozier.
科?你了,哈奇?
Cozier?Did you hear that,Hatch?
了
Yeah.
我可不回旅^ 一人乾坐著
I ain't going back to no hotel to sit on my own.
你不去旅^,
Right,you ain't going back to the hotel,
也不去什N加勒比海
you ain't going to the freaking Caribbean either.
你要回戒毒所^m戒毒
You're going back to the rehab to start your program again.
- 我不去!- 非去不可!
- Hell,no,I ain't!- Yes,you are!
我受蛄酸t生和o士著我的面
I'm tired of them nurses and doctors making you stand up
和陌生人我的情r
and chat your business in front of strangers.
你每次都@,每次都是出商煊秩ノ毒了!
Every time,you do the same thing!Every time!Two days out of rehab!
出商煊诌M警察局了
Just two days and you're in the police station already.
我o你的X呢?都I毒品了吧?
Where's the money I gave you?Is it in your veins?
你少管我的事
You know,your problem is you're too into my shit.
因槟悴辉诤踝约!
Let me see your arm.Your shit.You're not into your own shit!
你管你自己的事吧?你根本不在乎我
Why don't you get a life?You don't care about me.
都不我住在你那Y
You wouldn't even let me stay at your apartment.
- 嫌我G你的人 是我把你B活大的!
- That's right.- You're ashamed of me.And I raised you!
整天吸毒的人B活我?
You raised me?My crackhead sister raised me?
- 你B自己都B活不了 - 忘恩x的混蛋!
- Can't even raise yourself.- You ungrateful bastard!
- ef了 - 你算什N
- Shut up.- But you ain't worth shit,man.
- 初把你送人就好了!- 你f得
- I should've let Welfare take you!- You're right,you're right.
我真糊T
Wonder.
W米!
Naomi!
e走!W米!
No!Naomi!Naomi!
戈登科 20分前把她I走了
Gordon Cozier.Signed for her 20 minutes ago.
- 商鹊诙次到@名字了 - 是啊
- Second time in two days.- Yeah,I hear you.
即使@XC明是的,也不能C明是科筛傻
Even if we tie those bills to a certain job,it doesn't prove Cozier did anything.
F在提他的,只怕打草@蛇他跑了
Question him now,he lawyers up,splits town.We can blow this case.
只要能C明劫案天他M了梯,
If we can put him in the elevators on the day of the heist,
就有了足虻淖C
we'll have plenty to talk to him about.
到rg了 e再情f哿
It's time.Let's go,Casanova.
今晚再
I'll see you tonight.
你小心
You be careful.
- 我勰 - 我也勰
- I love you.- Love you,too.
快c,情}!走吧!
Come on,lover boy!Let's go,mate!
有正事呢 戆
Got a job to do,baby.Come on.
我走!
Let's go,let's go!
喝咖啡?是吃c心?
You want a coffee?Donut?Anything?
不用
Naw.I'm okay.
芸 卡沃找你
Hey,Jack.Carver wants to see you.
F在]空 FedCaly行劫案就要破了
Not now,Max.We're getting close on this FedCal job.
@不是求你,芸
It's not a request,Detective Welles.
@是命令
Orders,Jack.
好吧
All right.
你太弱了,警L
This is chicken shit,Chief.
海地人,俄_斯人 很多r候我都需要C立
The Haitian,the Russians.I make judgment calls every day.
- 我也有嗾律,
- The union says I get an attorney...- Before you go on about this,
- 就像被我揍的混蛋一
- you need to......just like the assholes
- 芸ef了!
- I gotta deal with out there.- Jack,stop!
5分後如果你想找律 可以o你
Look,if you still want to see a lawyer in five minutes,you can have one.
先坐下
Sit down.
趴下!趴在地上!
Get down!Get on the ground!Get on the ground!Spread your legs!
- 趴在地上- @是你突艉５厝,
- Keep your head down.- The day you busted the Haitian,
禁毒在街道γ姘惭b有z像^
Narcotics had surveillance set up in the building across the street.
- ]嘴!- 我f^他o你X!
- Shut up!Stay down!- I said they'd give you money!
- 什NX?- 就是@Y的X!
- What?What money?- Money,right there!
在那,e!好了你走吧
Stay there,don't move!All right.All right,get out of here.Go.
P了 P了吧
Turn it off.All right,turn it off.
我想你知道你的搭n是什N人
I wanted you to know who you were working with.
我X得先告V你
Felt I owed you that much.
詹恳提起指控 今天就在洳牧
Internal Affairs is bringing charges.Papers are being drawn up today.
你要送哈奇回家的我能理解
You wanna drop Hatcher?I understand.
怎N@
No,no.No.No.
的怎N?
How'd it go?
是老一套
You know,same old,same old.
Χ酒坟子也不哟
Shouldn't have roughed up that drug dealer,you know?
- 就@c事?-
- That's the beef?That's it?- Yeah.
o我警告
Warning,short and sweet.
你看看 就是他
Check it out.That's our guy.We got him.
i定科上壬了 我去找他吧
Time to turn up the heat on Mr.Cozier.Let's go pay him a visit.
一切就w 溟_工吧
All right,we're hot.Ready to rock,man.
好 P]信
All right.Kill the traffic light.
_始了
Let's go.
糖诮痪
Officer on duty.
好,警官 \n5分後到
All right,Officer.Package is due in five minutes.
哨O他
Crow's nest.Put an eye on him.
收到
Copy that.
你黹_
You're driving.
提提精神吧!
Come on,let's go!
你到底怎N了?
Come on,man.What's wrong with you?
你楹芜@N做,艾迪?
Why'd you do it,Eddie?
楹文米吣枪PX?
Why'd you take the money?
我不明白你的意思?
What are you...What are you talking about?
都下砹
They got it on tape.
你楹芜@N做?
Why'd you do it?
唉
Shit,man.
莫妮卡下了 要房J 保U金那N少
Monica's laid off.We got a mortgage.Insurance doesn't pay shit.
有孩子的tM
All these medical bills.
你一定要臀,芸
You gotta help me,Jack.
X[在我面前 我就忍不住拿了
It was right there.It was right there,and I took it.
有困y怎N不找我?
Why didn't you come to me?
我是小艾迪的教父呢
I'm Eddie's godfather.
你我情同手足
Come on.You're like my brother.
可我需要的X不是小,一子都瓴
The kind of money I'm talking about,you couldn't save it in a lifetime.
六年砟阋恢闭疹我
Look,you've had my back for the last six years.
我自然M全力湍,知道?
I'm gonna do whatever it takes to help you,okay?
好
Yeah.
\n]有
Package is late.
肯定有事耽R了 淼 真是的!老是┪
Must've gotten hung up.They'll be here.Goddamn!Get off my ass.
肯定有} 肯定有}
This is not good.This is not good.
要下手就f一,戈登,我浜昧
Let me know,G.I'm ready.
你要有信心
Come on,boys,have some faith.
我一直都信不^他 我得做些什N
I never trusted this guy.This is bad,we gotta do something.
在洛杉t到很正常
This is LA,man.Nothing runs on time.
我@Y一大堆C4炸,弄不好命都]了
Damn all that.We got a shitload of C-4,and we're live down here.Come on.
冷o
Just be cool,all right?
\n到底在哪?老鬼,告V我?
Where the hell is it,Ghost?Talk to me.Where is it?
真是的,肯定淼
They're coming,God damn it.They'll be here.
只要你下令,我就_
Say the word,G.I'll send it.
肯定淼 你急什N真是的!
Y'all need to relax.I told you they coming.Damn!
戈登,我不能坐以待
G,we gotta make a move.Come on,man.
ef了!
All right!
你在哪,s翰?
Where you at,John?
我知道你肯定在琼,混蛋
I know you up there,son of a bitch.
有什N情r?
Well?Is there anDhing?
]有 如果他要逃跑, @是最後值羲的C
Nada.If he bolts,this may be our last shot,right now.
- 戈登 - 大家都e急
- G.- Everybody,stay sharp.
肯淼闹皇峭砹艘稽c而已
They'll be here,G.Theyjust running a little behind.
我不能值戎了
We gotta do something.Come on.
快,怎N不?
Come on,bitch.Where are you?
值羲
Take him out.
砹!砹!我就f^!
They're here!They're here,God damn it!I told you they were coming!
好了,等等,等等!
All right,hold up,hold up!
都浜!
Buckle up,boys!
F在下了坡道
They're turning down the ramp now.
火要x站了
Train's about to leave the station.
戈登,他砹
A'ight,G.Here they come.
正前往第四大道
Merging onto 4th.
死的 不吧?
God damn it.You kidding me?
怎N停下了?
What's the holdup?
我正r住交通 o啊
Come on,guys,I'm holding traffic.Just give me the word.
目^域有汽
All right,boys,we've still got cars inside the cones here.
好,保持M
All right,keep me posted.
快啊
Come on.
快c啊!怎N了?
Come on,already!Yo,what's up?
- 我走吧!- 你不人走啊?
- Let's go!- You gonna move this or what?
我看目^域]了 o我
Cones look clear to me.Holla at me.
他通^吧,警官
Go on ahead and wave them through,Officer.
算走了!
Finally!
不_啊?
Where you going?
_始行恿!
Showtime,boys!
- 好了 - 好,行
- All right,it's on.- All right,here we go.
- _始吧!- F在看你的了!
- It's on!- It's in your hands now!
我赍X吧!
Let's get paid,man!
50a!
Fifty yards!
25a!10a!
Twenty-five yards!Ten yards!
- T的小心!- 引爆!
- Look out!Bike!- Hit it!
死的!T自行的!
Holy shit!Goddamn bicyclist!
死!
Shit!
- 你怎N?
- Jesus Christ!- You all right?
死的,提前了一cc!
Damn it,too soon!
\n在路面上!
I still see the trucks!
]炸到\n呢?
We missed!Where is it?
- o急x了 - 怎N回事?
- Truck stopped short.- What's going on?
- 真是的,芸,爆炸太早了
- Shit!- God damn it,Jake,you went too early.
你就]嘴吧,老鬼!
Shut up,Ghost,shut up!
街道l生爆炸!我遇U了 快x_!
The street blew up!We're in trouble.We gotta get out of here!
呆在Y!我z去接!
Stay in that truck!We'll get you out of this!
- 下疏Ы煌!- 戈登,F在怎Nk?
- Get out and move that traffic,let's go!- G,now what?
- 我怎Nk?- 哨!你在哪,哨?
- What we doing?- Crow's nest!Where are you,crow's nest?
- 芸,流a,我必走
- Talk to me,talk to me!- Jake,it's a bust,man.
- 我必走人!
- We gotta get out of here!- What are we doing,G?
- 我什N都看不!- 按!呆在!
- I can't see shit!- Follow procedure!Stay in that truck!
- 我走吧!
- Okay,let's clear this!- G,call it off!
- 都ef了
- No,no,hold on!- What are y'all doing?
戈登!
G!
取消行!取消行!
Abort!Abort!
一切都y套了!
All hell broke loose up here,man!
戈登!
G!
快走!@次行尤∠!
Let's go,let's go!We gotta abort this,we gotta abort this!
- 等等!我看有情r!
- Abort,abort!- Hold on,hold on!I see something up here!
有人在行
We got a man on the move.
不行,我R上取消行!
No,Officer,we're aborting this now!
先e急,有人在行!
Not yet,God damn it,we got action!
我在上面看得更清楚,戈登!先拖住他!
You don't see what I see,G!Just keep them busy!
@子要质颤N?
What's this crazy son of a bitch doing?
喂!
Hey!
天!他打倒了一警l!
Shit!He just jacked a guard!
_T!
Open this door!
他最I了一v!
We got a vehicular,people!
他上了!
He in the truck!
@子制砹!
Crazy son of a bitch is going for it!
他撞了!
He hit the car!
下面v出地方!
Keep it clear down below,boys!
- 天,他要砹!- 他砹,他砹!
- Shit,man,here he come!- Here he comes,here he comes!
他撞了前面的!
He's ramming the truck!
- 砹!- _!
- Here it come!- Get out of the way!
@硬,漂亮!
That's what I'm talking about!Damn!
- 拿工具!- 火力掩o!
- Get the jaws,get the jaws!- Keep them back!
混蛋!
Shit!Little bastard!
@砘镎媸悄大包天!
Soldier boy done lost his damn mind!
天!他要质颤N?
Shit!What's he doing?
他遇到麻┝
Our man got a problem here.
撞向警l!
Hit the guard!
下面小心!
Incoming!
好啊
Hell,yeah.
去接他!
Take his shit!
有我呢
I've got you,man.Come on.Got you.
成功了
We got it.
都注意\n劫案,第四大道和撖旖致房
All units,211 on an armored vehicle,4th and Olive.
重},\n劫案第四大道和橄旖致房
Repeat,armored vehicle robberyin progress,4th and Olive.
第四大道和橄旖致房 是他
4th and Olive.That's them.
掉^
Turn the car around.
我送你回家
I'm taking you home,Eddie.
掉^吧 x@Y很近
Come on,turn the car around.It's a couple blocks away.
- 不行 - 真是的,我]撤呢!
- No,man.- God damn it,man,I'm still a cop!
快掉^!
Turn the car around!
好吧
All right.
我快c!
Let's hustle,boys,come on!
耶!
Yeah!
- 快走,芸!
- Come on!- Come on,Jake!
走,走!
Go,go,go,go!
我走!
Yeah,let's go,let's go,let's go,let's go!
快走!
Move it,move it!
看
Look at this.
@可需要很多炸
Took a shitload of explosives to do this.
- C-4炸 -
- C-4.- Yeah.
- 有什N情r?- 奢v掉在洞Y
- What do you got?- We got two down in the hole.
警l看了其中一人
Guard got a look at one of them.
30多q的白人男性
Caucasian male,adult,in his 30s.
像正s
I got a sketch artist coming here now to work with our witness.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
他早就走了!下水道四通八_
They're long gone!Sewer tunnels in every direction.
下水道?
Sewer tunnels?
得我在俄人的Cc lF的市政工程D?
Remember that public works map we found at the Russian safe house?
被S的片?下水道,炸 高性能武器
The burnt fragment?The sewers,explosives.High-powered weapons.
他仍然劫了?
So the job went down without our two dead guys?
是的,你得俄人那Y有地F地D幔
Yeah,well,you remember the map?There was a subway map at the Russians.
你X得下水道通往地F站?
Yeah,you think the sewers connect to the subway station?
有可能,我去看看
Could be,let's check it out.
- 最近的地F站是哪Y?- 珀欣V
- What was the closest station circled?- Pershing Square.
借^
Pardon me.
就是他!戴灰帽子的!就在峁上出F^!
That's him,Hatch!The guy with the gray hat!From the hot-dog stand!
- 糟糕!- 不S!
- Shit!- Freeze!
- 看一逃跑的!- e跑!
- We have a runner!- Stop!
混蛋!
Asshole!
_,_!
Get out the way,get out the way!
心!心!
Look out!Look out!
- 你了?
- Are you crazy?- Shit!
]著吧?喂!你跑什N?
You all right?Hey!Where you going,pal?
我在追逐逃犯!
We're in pursuit!
前往珀欣V
Headed toward Pershing Square.
他跑^停!
He's headed through the park!
_ _
Move.Move.Move.
e碰我的!
Get off my car!Hey!
他x_了Grand!正前往D^!
He just left Grand!He's headed towards the library!
糟糕!
Shit!
警察!不S!
Police!Freeze!
_!
Move!
_!_!
Move,move,move,move!Get out the way!
警察!心!
Police!Watch out!
- 他去哪毫?- 那
- Which way did he go?- Back there.
- @Y有出口?- ]有
- Can we exit this way?- No.
- _!- 守住@T!
- Get out of the way!- Cover those doors!
- 走,走!- 他去了@方向
- Move,move,move!- He went that way.
- 他去了那Y - 去了大d
- He went that way.- Down the hall.
喂!
Hey!
_!
Move it!
喂!
Hey,hey!
_!_!
Get out of my way!Get out of my way!
都出去!
Everybody,out!
振作,芪
Come on,Jesse.
哈奇?
Hatch?
哈奇!
Hatch!
天啊!
Shit!
挺住,哥 挺住 天啊
Hold on,buddy.Just hold on.Jesus.
- @混蛋身手快 - 我是14M
- The son of a bitch was fast.- This is unit 14.
有警T受 T_大橇
I got an officer down.Sixth floor,Monroe building.
R上砭仍
I need immediate assistance.
不S!
Freeze!
他出去了!
He's outside!
挺住 M力呼吸,哥
Come on,come on.Just keep breathing,buddy.
M力呼吸 猿肿
Keep breathing.Come on,stay with me.
快砭茸o人T!快!
I need that crash unit fast!Now!
哥,猿肿
Come on,buddy.Hang in there.
他跑了!
We lost him!
我@是因公殉 因公殉
Line of duty,Jack.Line of duty.
ey想 你M力呼吸
Yeah,come on.Come on.You just keep breathing.
你一定要猿肿 看著我
You gotta make it,man.Come on.Look at me,look at me.
我的家人,莫妮卡 你照小艾迪
My family,man.Monica.You take care of Eddie.
我照你家人
I'm gonna take care of your family.Don't worry about that.
你放心 M力呼吸
They're gonna be taken care of.You just keep breathing.
- 挺住 - 告V莫妮卡我鬯
- Come on.- Tell Monica I love her.
- 我的 - f我鬯
- I will.- Tell her I love her.
挺住,哥 猿肿
Come on,buddy.Hang in there.
是我
It's me.
我知道你是l 我看了新 你我是傻子?
I know who it is.I watch news.You think I'm stupid,you punk bitch?
e上火啊 你何必@N生饽
Hey,cool it,brother.I sense a little too much hostility.
我只是榱舜蠹
I was just trying to make everybody...
我把{度To了你,你s找e人干了!
I give you dispatcher,and you do job with somebody else!
我死了手下 我要⒘四!
Two of my men dead.I kill you!
不的 如果我死了,怎No你一半的X呢?
You do not wanna kill me.If I'm dead,how am I gonna get you half the money?
你想要X吧?
You do want the money,don't you?
F在消饬税?我就知道
You listening now?Thought so.
我在_斯福酒店面 我f服他o你一半
Hey,we meeting at the Roosevelt Hotel.I'm gonna convince them to give you half.
等我告V你房g
I'll call you later with the room number.
我都很y^,芸 我和他妻子M了
We're all real sorry,Jack.I just spoke with his wife.
O控像的事怎Nk?考]一下他的家人?
What about the surveillance tape?His family?
管什N像啊 他因公殉
Forget the tape.He was killed in the line of duty.
樗e行正式葬Y,全~嵝艚
He'll get a cop's burial and full benefits.
那就好 xx
Good.Thanks.
你在FedCaly行劫案上有了突破 是同一夥人?
You were making headway with FedCal Bank.Was it them?
不知道 我看有人跑就追上去了
I don't know.Guy started running,we chased him.
艾迪中 我也]抓住他
Eddie got shot.I got nothing.
你不要o吧,芸?
You okay,Jack?
我]事
Yeah.I'm fine.
- 芸?有芪鞯南息?- ]有
- Jake?You heard from Jesse?- No,not yet.
目前是1930f美元 p到最大的一P
$19.3 million,so far.Easily the biggest lick yet,gentlemen.
目粽叻Q
Witnesses report...
只怕他出事了
I can feel it,man.Something's not right.
都怪我 我不他⒓拥
This is my fault,man.I should've never brought him in.
- 老鬼?- 什N?
- Hey,Ghost?- Yes,sir?
好
Yeah.
@是04年劫案π羁
That's the account card for the '04 job.
@是o俄人的25f
That's $250,000 for the Russians.
我的で辶,老鬼
That puts us even now,Ghost.
你f什N,拉威?
Say what,Rahway?
你了 我的で辶
You heard me.That puts us even.
是啊 我的,你的指]
Yeah,a'ight.My plan,your command.
我就知道你靠得住
I knew I could trust y'all.
是l?
Who is it?
是他 你去哪毫?我一直o你打!
It's him.Where you been?I been calling you!
- 警察追我 - 警察?在哪?
- Police chased me.- Police?Where?
你把他引砹?芪?
You brought them here?Jesse,you brought them here?
] 我打中了一
No.I shot one of them.
- 什N?- 什N?
- What?- What?
- ef!你_打了警察?- 我]k法
- Hold on!You shot a cop?- I had to,man.
- X呢?- 藏起砹
- Where the money?- I stashed it.
- 你把X留下了!
- You left the money?Damn!- Goddamn!
都ef!什N情r,跟我ff
Stashed it?Hold,hold on!Everyone,hold on.What happened,Jesse?Talk to me.
在地F站,有警察
At the subway station,there was two cops.
然後他就追我
And they just started chasing me.
地F那N多人 槭颤N就追你呢?
And they chased you out the crowd because of what?
我怎N知道?
How,how the hell am I supposed to know?
- 槭颤N?- 老鬼 ef了
- Why?- Ghost.Hold on.
- ef了!
- Hold on!Hold on!- No,man,let him tell me why!
- 我哪知道槭颤N!
- So,what happened?You shot because?- I don't know!
- 你楹λ_?
- I had to.He had me...- Why'd you shoot him?
因槟闶潜康
'Cause you stupid.
]k法!他把我堵住
I had no choice!He had me.He had me cold,man.
可他]_ 感X就像
But he never fired at me.It was...It was kind of like...
像什N?
Like what?
好像他希望我_
Like he wanted me to shoot him.
笨蛋!
Stupid ass!
我揍死你
Shit!I'll beat the shit out of you.
- 放_他!
- G!G!Wait!- Let him go!Let him go!
你e拉我!走_!
Get off me!Yo,cool it.Get your hands off me!
- 你知道你做了什N?
- Back off!Back off!- You understand what you just did?
- @不怪我!- Q不能警察_!
- It wasn't my fault!- You don't shoot cops!
我自理!放_他!
I'll deal with it!Let him go!
那你去理吧,芸!
You deal with it then,Jake!
@可是死刑的罪名,年p人,我不陪你的
That's a death sentence,young blood,and I ain't going with you.
你真行,芪
Nice one,Jesse.
今晚能起w?
Still taking passengers tonight?
凡奈斯C,8c半
Van Nuys Airport,8:30.
今天的事只是生意,
Look,with everything that happened today,nothing personal,
我打理你的X,然後我就走
I'll take care of your finances and then I'm out.
- 好 - @涌梢
- Okay.- Fair enough.
我F在正站在洛杉市^
I'm standing about a block awayfrom the Monroe office building
距xT_大且街^
in downtown Los Angeles
一小r前一位洛杉警察在茄Y被
where an LAPD detectivewas shot and killed about an hour ago.
r到
Right on time.
目粽叻Q
Witnesses describe...
芪鞔蛩懒司察 又G了X,是什N感X?
So,Jesse,how'd it feel losing that money,shooting that cop?
- 老鬼行了
- Ghost.Easy.- What?
目前o法_J,但嫌疑犯
Now,we can't confirm,at this hour,but the suspect...
老鬼,你F在不假b我是朋友了?
Ghost,we ain't gotta act like we friends anymore,do we?
喂,生意是生意 X是X
Hey,business is business.Money is money.
我可]f^我是朋友
I never said we were friends.
- 不^我和莉莉是朋友 - 你^!
- Now,me and Lilli,however.- Come here!You wanna...
e激!芸,芸!
Hey!Take it easy!Hey,Jake,Jake,Jake!
e激!他不值得你上火
Hey,come on,take it easy!He's not worth it,all right?
都把人叫上 x_@Y吧
All right,let's get the fellas and get out of here.
我砹 哪房g?
I'm here.Which room?
1116 好
1116.A'ight.
威士,你在哪?有什N情r?
Hey,Welles,where you at?You got a 20?
我知道你能 回
Come on,man,I know you're out there.Pick up.
我都心你
We're worried about you.Where you...
好了,各位,我走吧
All right,fellas,we're good.We're out of here.
下面@ 如果l想去
So,here's the deal.Anyone wants to fly with...
- 老鬼呢?- 在l生g
- Where's Ghost?- In the bathroom.
叫他
Get Ghost for me.
今晚,斯考特,8:30,凡奈斯C
Tonight,Scott,8:30,Van Nuys Airport,all right?
wC浜昧 上o照,行李,手
Plane's ready.Bring your passports,your bags,and your guns.
老鬼?喂!
Ghost?Hey!
有什N需要,o我打
If you need anything,make sure you give us a call.
他在质颤N,洗澡?
What's he doing,taking a shower?What's going on in here?
- 怎N了?- 淋浴_著
- What was that?- Shower's on.
他不了!
Hey,he's gone!
- 我就f^!我就f^!
- I told you!I told you!- What?
- 不至於吧!
- I don't know about this.- Damn!
- 他去哪毫?
- What are you talking about?- Where'd he go?
- 我就知道有}!
- I knew this was a bad idea!- Damn it!
我x_@Y,我x_@Y
Let's get out of here,let's get out.
天!
Oh,shit!
拿出自硬!
Take out the automatic!
芪!
Jesse!
芸,你怎N?
Hey,Jake,you okay?
起!快起!快!
Get up,man,get up!Come on,buddy!Come on,man,come on!
- 走後T!- 芪,芸,我走!
- Out the back!- Jesse,Jake,let's go!
我快走!
Come on,let's go!
走 我S後就
Go.I'm coming.
走!
Go!
快,快!
Come on,come on!
A J呢?他在哪?
Where's A.J?Where's A.J?Where's...
P倒!
Down,get down!
- 他是什N人?- 口音是俄人!
- Shit!Who are these guys?- Sounds like Russians!
芸!去看看走廊
Jake!Check the hallway.
我把床抬起,!
Let's put these beds up,let's go!
走廊有人守著!
We got a shotgun in the hallway!
P倒,P倒!
Stay low,stay low!
死!我]子了!
Shit!I'm out of ammo!I'm out,I'm out!
芸四?
Where's Jake?
我走了,各位 我走了
We gotta go,fellas.We gotta go.
老鬼我和俄人火拚
Ghost set us up against the Russians.
混蛋,他肯定也把提供o了他
Son of a bitch,he must've sold them on the same plan.
所以他把{度To他
That's why they gave him the dispatcher
}促劫 就是榱俗我先邮
and that big hurry-up was just to get us to do the job first.
- ,我上了 - 氐咨袭了
- Yeah,and we bought it.- Yeah,all of it.
@一片很快要封i了
Shit,the heat's gonna be coming down now.
是啊 我C鲆
I know.See you at the airport.
莉莉?莉莉?
Lilli?Lilli?
猿肿,H鄣 起
Hold on,baby.Oh,God,baby,get up.Baby.
天啊,H鄣,醒醒
Oh,my God,baby,wake up.Oh,just...
死的,X不了!
Goddamn,the money's gone!
芪,臀!
Jesse,help me!Help me!
老鬼,我要⒘四
Ghost.Ghost,I'm gonna kill you.Oh,God.
芸,有人砹
Jake,we got company.
芸,我必走了
Jake,we gotta go.We have to go.
天,老鬼
Oh,God.Ghost.
我是洛杉警察慢慢走出房子
Los Angeles Police Department.Exit the building slowly.
限你20秒之茸叱
You have 20 seconds to come out.
芸,我看e了老鬼
Look,Jake.I was wrong about Ghost.
Σ黄
I'm sorry,man.
@不怪你
It's not your fault.
芪髂悴槐嘏阄颐半U
Jesse,you ain't gotta be down with me on this one.
你要考]自己未淼纳活
You got your own life to think about,man.
我f^了,^不再回Oz
I already told you.I'm never going back.
@就是我的生活
And this is my life.
我的在後面你的呢?
My car's out back.Where's yours?
在前面
In front.
我坐你的
Let's take yours.
知道你@Nf
Thought you'd say that.
浜昧,兄弟?
You ready,bro?
我兄弟一起走吧
Just me and you,big brother.Let's go.
- W米 - 戈登!
- Naomi.- G!
- 你质颤N? - 戈登!
- What are you doing?Come here.- G!
你怎N在@?]事吧?
What are you doing?Are you all right?
- 他不我x_ - 我必走
- They won't let me in your building.- We've gotta go.
,我上
Come on,let's get in the car.All right.
- 我只想回老家 - 好
- Just wanna go home.- All right.
看你了
There you are.
- f - 我快到C隽
- Talk to me.- I'm almost to the airport.
我也是
Yeah,me,too.
我在琢磨一件事 我握ff?
Hey,I'm tripping.Hear me out right quick,all right?
怎N了?
Yeah,what's up?
老鬼一_始就在耍弄我
Ghost has had the jump on us from the get-go,right?
那他槭颤N把我都值
So,why would he take us all out
s只M足於得到04年的那PX呢?
and then only settle for the cash from the '04 job?
- 他不的 - 除非
- He wouldn't.- Unless...
- 他打算把X都拿走 - X都在斯考特那Y
- Man,he plans on taking all the money.- Shit,Scott.Scott has all the money.
]e 我@就去 跟著你去
Exactly.I'm on my way.I'm right behind you.
我知道很晚了 他和我在y行面
I know this is a little last-minute.Have him meet me at the bank.
斯考特,快接 接
Come on,Scott,pick up.Scott,pick up.
我今晚就去
Yeah,I'm coming in tonight.
你明天早上9c要有空,好?
You have to make yourself available at 9:00 a.m.Tomorrow,all right?
你能做到?
Can you do that?
我是斯考特 F在我不在
You've reached Scott.I'm away from my cell.
斯考特,快接 真是的
Oh,God.No,Scott,pick up.Damn it.
好
All right.
好了我走吧
Okay.Let's get out of here.
今天累牧 能o我倒一杯酒?
It's been a long day.Can you pour me a Scotch?
你去哪? 你一定要吞啊,老鬼?
Yeah,where are you going?You just had to have it all,didn't you,Ghost?
- 我只是拿走我的X!- 是?
- I'm just taking what's mine!- Oh,yeah?
今天在街上就打死你
I should've shot you on the street today.
不,5年前你就把我打死在翘萆
Naw,you should've shot me five years ago on that fire escape.
是你被抓住了,老鬼!你被抓住了!
You got caught,Ghost!You got caught!
你知道我的s定!
You knew the game when you was playing it!
你把我G下不管!
You left me back there to die like I was shit!
不是不管你!
You ain't shit,Ghost!
我湍惆殃伍M起!
I helped you put this crew together!
你F在又想拆散伍?
So what?Now you wanna take it apart?
放下武器!警察!放下武器!
Drop the weapon!Drop it!Police!Put them down!
- 放下!- 放下!
- Put them down!- Stay out of this!
- @是我z的恩怨
- Better listen to him,cop.- It's between me and him.
你干涉的,我把你也⒘
If you interfere,I'm gonna kill you,too.
- 最後f一遍,放下武器!
- Last time,drop them!- Shit.
我能怎N做,戈登?
What you expect me to do,G?Huh?
拿走了我的X 走了我的女人
You took my money.Took my bitch from me.
把我s出了伍?
Just put me out the crew,huh?
我以槲忘那?
What you thought I was gonna do?Let that shit go?
你被抓住了!
You got caught!
好 我F在明白了
Yeah.A'ight.I see now.
你只看成公事公k
It's all business for you.
但我X得是私人恩怨
Well,this shit just got real personal.
- 你等著我的 - 他值锰快了
- Should've waited for me,G.- The shit went too fast.
等等,等等
Hold,hold it,hold it,hold it.
e!你e!
Don't move!Don't you move!
那天就是你跟我
You're that cop with the little girl.
你不插手的
You should've stayed out of this.
- 我上X走吧 - 好
- Let's get that money and get out of here.- Yeah.
救o中心
Emergency dispatch.
Yeah.
有警察受 凡奈斯C12C
You got an officer down.Van Nuys Airport,hangar 12.
我中了需要救助
I've been shot and I need help.
R上就到
Units en route.
我想兔
I want help.
戈登?我F在回老家?
G?Are we going home now?
,我回老家
Yeah,baby.We're going home.
情r怎N?
Are we good,brother?
一切都好
All signs point to it.